London is not going to know what hit it!
Bill is a comedy, family film directed by Richard Bracewell.
What really happened during Shakespeare's 'Lost Years'?
Hopeless lute player Bill Shakespeare leaves his home to follow his dream.
William 'Bill' Shakespeare / Lord Burghley / English Messenger
/ Customs Official, played by Mathew Baynton.
Earl of Croydon / Juan Domingo / Sausage / Dmitri
Alexandrovitch / Fur Seller, played by Simon Farnaby.
Anne Hathaway / Molly / Spanish Courtier / Body
Collector, played by Martha Howe-Douglas.
Christopher Marlowe / Gabriel Montoya / Cynical Jester / Palace Doorman /
Mysterious Man / Even Grubbier Thief / Party Planner, played by Jim Howick.
Sir Francis Walsingham / Lope Lopez / Stand-Up Jester / Chatty Guard / Slightly Late
Courtier / Ian / Hanging Criminal / Chicken Drumstick, played by Laurence Rickard.
King Phillip II of Spain / Earl of Southampton / Grubby Thief / Alexander
Dimitrievitch / Head of Guards, played by Ben Willbond.
Bill is a 2015 British family adventure comedy film from the principal performers
behind children's TV series Horrible Histories and Yonderland.
It was produced by Punk Cinema, Cowboy Films and BBC Films and was
released in the UK on 18 September 2015 by Vertigo Films.
The film is a fictional take on the young William Shakespeare's search for fame and fortune, as written by Laurence Rickard and Ben
Willbond and directed by Richard Bracewell who co-produced with Tony Bracewell, Alasdair Flind and Charles Steel.
It features the six lead performers playing several different roles each including Mathew Baynton,
Martha Howe-Douglas, Ben Willbond, Simon Farnaby, Jim Howick and Laurence Rickard.
Bill has received mostly positive reviews from
critics and grossed $968,534 worldwide.
The film also received nominations for the Evening Standard British Film Award for
Award for Comedy and the Into Film Award for Family Film of the Year.
The tone is lighthearted.